prottapp.com 2019-06-11

# Prott - Prototyping tool. Privacy Policy

Goodpatch Inc. (hereinafter referred to as “Company”), realizing that personal information is the important property of an individual, has stated the following policies on treatment of personal information to appropriately collect and use personal information, to comply with laws and ordinances related to personal information and to prevent and cure leakage of personal information, and will take the best care in control and use of personal information. Please note that any collection of personal information by linked sites or any other entities is not covered by this Privacy Policy.

#### Appropriate Collection and Purpose of Use

The Company will collect personal information through appropriate methods for the following purposes:

  * to provide the Company’s services;
  * to provide notices and send questionnaires regarding the Company’s services that are currently provided or under consideration for future releases;
  * to help improve the services and develop new services;
  * to make contact with you;
  * to verify your identity and otherwise respond to inquiries;
  * to select in drawings and deliver prizes or products;
  * to transmit advertisement information sponsored by the Company or any other third party;
  * to create statistical data regarding the use of the Company’s services;
  * to prevent any use in breach of the Terms of Service.

#### Appropriate Control and Protection

Personal information will be strictly controlled, and appropriate measures will be taken to prevent and cure unauthorized access, loss, destruction, falsification, and leakage of personal information.

#### Entrustment

The Company may entrust the whole or part of the personal information it collected to outsourcing entities to the extent required to achieve the purpose of use. In such case, the Company will fully examine the eligibility of such outsourcing entities, state confidentiality provisions in the contracts with them, and provide any necessary and appropriate supervision to them.

#### Provision to Third Party

The Company will not disclose or provide any data to any third party except when  
a prior consent is given by you;  
it is based on laws and ordinances;  
any breach of the Terms of Service for Prott or other Company’s services should occur, and there are sufficient reasons for determining the disclosure of the personal information is necessary to protect the Company’s rights, property and services;  
it is necessary for the protection of the life, body or property of an individual and is difficult to obtain your consent;  
it is specially necessary for improving public health or promoting the sound growth of children and is difficult to obtain your consent;  
it is necessary for cooperating with a national or local authority or an entity entrusted by it in executing the affairs prescribed by laws and ordinances, and obtaining your consent is likely to impede the execution of such affairs; or  
any succession of the Company’s business including the provision of personal information is made due to any merger, company split, transfer of operations or other reasons.

#### Joint Use

The Company may jointly use any personal information with the Company’s business cooperators in providing the Company’s services. In such case, the Company will, in advance, publish the items of the personal information used jointly, the scope of the joint users, the purpose for which the personal information is used jointly and the name of person responsible for the management of the personal information is used jointly.

#### Use by minors under 18

If you are under 18, please use the Company’ service and input the personal information upon the consent of your custodian.

#### Procedures for Disclosure

The Company will respond without delay to your request for notice of the purpose of use, disclosure, correction, addition or deletion of contents, discontinuance of the use, erasure, and discontinuance of provision to a third party (hereinafter referred to as “Disclosure, etc.”) of (your) personal information. Provided, however, you are required to take the procedures prescribed by the Company in requesting Disclosure, etc.

#### Disclaimer

The Company shall assume no liability whatsoever if you reveal the personal information to third parties using any feature of the Company’s services or any other means and you become identifiable by such information you disclosed on the Company’s services.

#### Creation and Use of Statistical Data

The Company may crate, based on the personal information collected, statistical data processed so that no individual is identifiable. With regard to such creation and use of the personally unidentifiable statistical data, the Company may conduct without any restriction.

#### Collection and Use of Attribute Information/Activity History

The Company may collect and/or use the following personally unidentifiable information to personalize the Company’s services or contents of advertisements and may provide such information to sponsors, information providers, or service providers: cookies, logs, activity histories for accessed URLs, contents or reference orders, individual terminal identification information and other device information, and attribute information on gender, occupation, or age.

#### Amendment

The Company may amend the whole or part of this Privacy Policy. Any material amendment shall be announced on the Company’s website.

#### Contact Point

The Company will endeavor to respond appropriately to your inquiries regarding the treatment of the personal information. To make any inquiries about the treatment of personal information by the Company, please contact the following:  
Goodpatch Inc.  
Attn: Personal Information Treatment Inquiry Office  
VORT Shibuya south 2nd Floor,  
3-3 Uguisudanicho, Shibuya-ku, Tokyo  
Email:[ info@prottapp.com](mailto:info@prottapp.com)

#### Start your free 30-day trial now!

The free trial includes unlimited access to all features of the Pro plan. No credit card information required. Free forever.

#### Help us understand who you are

After the trial period ends, your account will be automatically downgraded to the Free plan.

Already have an account? Sign in.

After the trial period ends, your account will be automatically downgraded to the Free plan.

Already have an account? Sign in.

nexus 5iPhone 6MacBook Bordericon-billicon-communicationRectangle 54 + Rectangle 54contactdesign-processetuPage 1Oval 63 + Oval 63Group 11GroupGroupRectangle 107 + Rectangle 107 + Rectangle 107 + Oval 57 + Oval 57 + Path 192 Copy 16 + Oval 57 + Path 192 Copy 16Page 1Page 1GroupGroupRectangle 54 + Rectangle 54previewGroupicon-seminarGroupRectangle 107 + Rectangle 107 + Rectangle 107 + Oval 57 + Oval 57 + Path 192 Copy 16 + Oval 57 + Path 192 Copy 16Oval 63 + Oval 63icon-user-supportGroupadwaysanyperkbizreachcookpaddenaPage 1greeideoignismixirecruitunitedustwovoyagegroupyahoo!japanzappallasimages/icon/logoanyperkbizreachcookpadimage/icon/DeNAFill 2ideorecruitrhizomatiksustwoyahoo!japanarrowarrowarrow
